[EPIC]⚡ Go ahead.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 I'm... Spider. Get out of the way! Take me with the bitch! Get you a bitch, bitch! Get you a bitch, bitch!
[EPIC]⚡ And sometimes Spider-Man has to...
[EPIC]⚡ even if it.
[EPIC]⚡ is hard.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 Thank you.
[EPIC]⚡ Oh, God. Oh, God. Oh, God. Oh, God. Excuse me, Dr. Batter? I need your help. What do you say your name was? 15A's, Mewtwo.
[EPIC]⚡ enormously dangerous. Spiders have three life cycles. When between cycles, it can be despite a vulnerable to threats. We are faced with a danger, but we can't control. One we can't even see. Stay out of my way. You lose in a kid and for those spiders who make it through, it amounts to a kind of... Re-birth. Nice flower. Nice flower.
[EPIC]⚡ .
[DIALOGUE]🗣 Bye bye.
[SILENCE]🤫 Okay.